While I recognize that most of my previous jobs have been in Food Service and I have culinary experience, I've been studying about Web Development/Design for just under a year with a mentor who has decades of experience.

I've taken courses paid and free on places like freeCodeCamp, The Odin Project, The Modern JavaScript Tutorial and a course given by Simo Edwin (developedbyed) on both React and the trio of HTML, CSS, and JS respectively. I want to get whatever kind of experience I can to get into the field and learn all I can from it. Thank you for taking the time to look at my resume!

Justin Lemos

23695 Brittany Ln. Sherwood, OR 97140 | 541-228-2538 | justinlemos24@yahoo.com | https://www.justinlemos.com

Skills

- Customer Service
- Good time management and ability to multitask
- Ability to work in teams or solo and follow instructions thoroughly
- Flexible under strict time-frames and able to work in a fast-paced environment
- Able to lift 25 lbs or more within reason
- Knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JS along with some React

Work Experience

Avamere Riverpark of Eugene

October 2017 – October 2019 · Eugene, OR

Organized residents' tickets for meals every day. Worked in pairs to wash dishes before and after service. Cleaned, sanitized and closed kitchen.

Provisions Market Hall

November 2019 – September 2021 · Eugene, OR

Worked in teams for baking, cutting and portioning dough to fill orders for other restaurants. Worked solo for bake off, and closed up the bakery after my shift ended. Helped to prep and make a variety of pastries and cookies in teams during early mornings according to order forms.

Marley's Monsters

September 2021 – August 2022 · Eugene, OR

Lead for a small team of four, laying out and cutting bulk amounts of fabric to be sewn. Gained warehouse experience, including operating a pallet-loader for storing pallets up high and unloading trucks. Gained experience at using NetSuite for inventory and filling work orders, as well as receiving shipments.

Education

Willamette High School · Eugene, OR

2010 - 2014

High School Diploma

Oregon Coast Culinary Institute · Coos Bay, OR

2015 - 2017

Associate's Degree of Applied Science in Culinary Arts

References

Lisa - Supervisor at Marley's Monsters: 541-972-1502